[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["West Virginia"]}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "How are you feeling after all this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "feeling", "after", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "I drove to West Virginia today, Piers, so I'm feeling very good right now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "drove", "to", "West", "Virginia", "today", ",", "Piers", ",", "so", "I", "'m", "feeling", "very", "good", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What kind of pledges can you give going forward?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "pledges", "can", "you", "give", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "First of all, they tell me how bad things looked on what they've seeing.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "they", "tell", "me", "how", "bad", "things", "looked", "on", "what", "they", "'ve", "seeing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "I mean, what is your view if you were being this passionate about it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "is", "your", "view", "if", "you", "were", "being", "this", "passionate", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Piers, the only thing I can tell you is without trying to find some (inaudible) or whatever some words that would describe it.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "the", "only", "thing", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "is", "without", "trying", "to", "find", "some", "(", "inaudible", ")", "or", "whatever", "some", "words", "that", "would", "describe", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "What are you going to do about this young renegade who doesn't really care about being reasonable?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "about", "this", "young", "renegade", "who", "does", "n't", "really", "care", "about", "being", "reasonable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, I know Ted.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "know", "Ted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What about putting him on Cruz point man to point man?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "putting", "him", "on", "Cruz", "point", "man", "to", "point", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Cory is going to be welcome (ph) edition.", "answer_tokens": ["Cory", "is", "going", "to", "be", "welcome", "(", "ph", ")", "edition", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Is that your take on the whole thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "take", "on", "the", "whole", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "How can he be stopped and how dangerous and how potentially powerful is he as a rival faction to moderate (ph) republicans?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "he", "be", "stopped", "and", "how", "dangerous", "and", "how", "potentially", "powerful", "is", "he", "as", "a", "rival", "faction", "to", "moderate", "(", "ph", ")", "republicans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":", "NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, I don't think he is particularly dangerous unless the American people find his message accurate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "is", "particularly", "dangerous", "unless", "the", "American", "people", "find", "his", "message", "accurate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "... could he still work the system to force one?", "question_tokens": ["...", "could", "he", "still", "work", "the", "system", "to", "force", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "How (inaudible) are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "(", "inaudible", ")", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "``", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "It's nice to be here.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "nice", "to", "be", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Why did it come to this and how do we avoid happening all over again in January?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "it", "come", "to", "this", "and", "how", "do", "we", "avoid", "happening", "all", "over", "again", "in", "January", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "EINER: Well, unfortunately I don't see a dynamic that it changes all that much.", "answer_tokens": ["EINER", ":", "Well", ",", "unfortunately", "I", "do", "n't", "see", "a", "dynamic", "that", "it", "changes", "all", "that", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, I mean, there's two things here that makes me laugh.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "there", "'s", "two", "things", "here", "that", "makes", "me", "laugh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "What do you want to say to this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "to", "say", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Is it Chris Christie or is it actually potentially someone like Ted Cruz?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "Chris", "Christie", "or", "is", "it", "actually", "potentially", "someone", "like", "Ted", "Cruz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Well, I see no reason why this dynamic won't play out in the primary context.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "see", "no", "reason", "why", "this", "dynamic", "wo", "n't", "play", "out", "in", "the", "primary", "context", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie", "Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "And if so, does he deserve more support about it getting right now?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "so", ",", "does", "he", "deserve", "more", "support", "about", "it", "getting", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Well, I think if you look at Ted Cruz and what he could have.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "if", "you", "look", "at", "Ted", "Cruz", "and", "what", "he", "could", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "The question is who can do that?", "question_tokens": ["The", "question", "is", "who", "can", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I have to wrap it up there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "wrap", "it", "up", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "How did you come up with that message?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "come", "up", "with", "that", "message", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "That is something that I tell him when he threw something in school.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "something", "that", "I", "tell", "him", "when", "he", "threw", "something", "in", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Do you believe in your heart after all this time that he's still alive?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "in", "your", "heart", "after", "all", "this", "time", "that", "he", "'s", "still", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "What do you feel in your gut?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "in", "your", "gut", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I feel that someone has him and holding him because there's not a surveillance tape around that shows him at all in a train station, out walking in the street, anywhere.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "that", "someone", "has", "him", "and", "holding", "him", "because", "there", "'s", "not", "a", "surveillance", "tape", "around", "that", "shows", "him", "at", "all", "in", "a", "train", "station", ",", "out", "walking", "in", "the", "street", ",", "anywhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "If he was down there, with all the attention that is now received, do you believe that he would've been discovered now, is that's why you feel he must have been taken against his will?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "was", "down", "there", ",", "with", "all", "the", "attention", "that", "is", "now", "received", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "he", "would", "'ve", "been", "discovered", "now", ",", "is", "that", "'s", "why", "you", "feel", "he", "must", "have", "been", "taken", "against", "his", "will", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Do you believe Vanessa that the school was negligent?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "Vanessa", "that", "the", "school", "was", "negligent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vanessa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "They should never let him out of the school, it should have been impossible?", "question_tokens": ["They", "should", "never", "let", "him", "out", "of", "the", "school", ",", "it", "should", "have", "been", "impossible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "I mean, do you think that could have happened?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "could", "have", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Even though he's 14, it shouldn't matter.", "answer_tokens": ["Even", "though", "he", "'s", "14", ",", "it", "should", "n't", "matter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Vanessa, if by any chance he's able to watch this interview either now or when is replayed perhaps tomorrow or somebody who was holding him as you believe is watching you, what would your message be first to Avonte and then to perhaps somebody who maybe holding him?", "question_tokens": ["Vanessa", ",", "if", "by", "any", "chance", "he", "'s", "able", "to", "watch", "this", "interview", "either", "now", "or", "when", "is", "replayed", "perhaps", "tomorrow", "or", "somebody", "who", "was", "holding", "him", "as", "you", "believe", "is", "watching", "you", ",", "what", "would", "your", "message", "be", "first", "to", "Avonte", "and", "then", "to", "perhaps", "somebody", "who", "maybe", "holding", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "TO", "RB", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "My message to my son is, that I love him and we'll going to find him, you'll come home to your family.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "message", "to", "my", "son", "is", ",", "that", "I", "love", "him", "and", "we", "'ll", "going", "to", "find", "him", ",", "you", "'ll", "come", "home", "to", "your", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "So, Star Jones would it (ph) been better off to kick all the men out of the rooms here in Washington and let the women trash (ph) it out or is that just a terrible cliche that actually (inaudible) wouldn't have actually made any difference?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "Star", "Jones", "would", "it", "(", "ph", ")", "been", "better", "off", "to", "kick", "all", "the", "men", "out", "of", "the", "rooms", "here", "in", "Washington", "and", "let", "the", "women", "trash", "(", "ph", ")", "it", "out", "or", "is", "that", "just", "a", "terrible", "cliche", "that", "actually", "(", "inaudible", ")", "would", "n't", "have", "actually", "made", "any", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", ":", "VBN", "JJR", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "NN", ":", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Well, actually we did make a difference.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", "we", "did", "make", "a", "difference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Oh you wouldn't?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", "you", "would", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I think you're totally sexist.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "totally", "sexist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "And all women is instinctive (inaudible) you think less testosterone field?", "question_tokens": ["And", "all", "women", "is", "instinctive", "(", "inaudible", ")", "you", "think", "less", "testosterone", "field", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Well, there's no question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "I tell you what?", "question_tokens": ["I", "tell", "you", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Let me hear what you got to say.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "hear", "what", "you", "got", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Well, you're saying that the have a lion share of the practicality of the household, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'re", "saying", "that", "the", "have", "a", "lion", "share", "of", "the", "practicality", "of", "the", "household", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "You have to be pragmatic.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "be", "pragmatic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Did you see that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "... how we've been.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "how", "we", "'ve", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kay Bailey Hutchison"]}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "What you make of Ted Cruz down in Texas?", "question_tokens": ["What", "you", "make", "of", "Ted", "Cruz", "down", "in", "Texas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I don't think Kay Bailey Hutchison knows who is calming down the fight.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "Kay", "Bailey", "Hutchison", "knows", "who", "is", "calming", "down", "the", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"], "LOCATION": ["Texas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz", "Ted Cruz"]}, "docId": "131017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Do you not believe that Ted Cruz is sincere?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "not", "believe", "that", "Ted", "Cruz", "is", "sincere", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I think that Ted Cruz is very focus on Ted Cruz.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "Ted", "Cruz", "is", "very", "focus", "on", "Ted", "Cruz", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}}]